crunkatlanta.com 2017-12-12

# Online Privacy Policy for Crunkatlanta.com

**ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT**

CrunkAtlanta is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those 

individuals that visit our website and make use of our on-line facilities and services accurate, 

confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure 

those affiliated with CrunkAtlanta of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only 

to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards. 

**THEREFORE** , this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to CrunkAtlanta and thus it shall 

govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of crunkatlanta.com you 

are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.

 **Collection of Information**

This website collects various types of information, such as:

  *  Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, 

billing and/or credit card information etc., which may be used when you purchase 

products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested.

  *  Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include 

cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs. 

Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly 

and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the 

intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested 

and any additional uses specifically provided on this site. 

CrunkAtlanta may also have the occasion to collect anonymous demographic information 

that may not be unique to you and may even gather additional or other personal and/or non-

personal information, such as age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and 

religion, at a later time.

It is even possible that we may gather information about your computer hardware and/or 

software. Such collected information may include, but may not be limited to, your IP 

address, browser type, domain name, access time and various website addresses. The 

gathering of this information may be used for maintaining the quality of service we provide, 

as well as providing overall general statistics related to the use of our website and others. 

It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and 

statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand 

the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected. 

**  
Use of Information Collected**

CrunkAtlanta may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the 

operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At 

times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information meant to inform 

you of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from 

crunkatlanta.com and its subsidiaries and may also be in contact with you with regards to 

completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or 

possible new services that are offered or may be offered.

CrunkAtlanta does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of its customer 

lists and/or names to any third parties.

CrunkAtlanta, from time to time, may feel it necessary to make contact with you on behalf 

of other external business partners with regards to a specific offer which may be of interest 

to you. If you consent or show interest in presented offers, then, at that time, specific 

identifiable information, such as name, email address and/or telephone number, may be 

shared with the third party. 

CrunkAtlanta may find it beneficial to share specific data with their trusted partners in an 

effort to conduct statistical analysis, provide you with email and/or postal mail, deliver 

support and/or arrange for deliveries to be made. Those third parties shall be strictly 

prohibited from making use of your personal information, other than to deliver those services 

which you requested, and as such they are thus required in accordance with this agreement 

to maintain the confidentiality of all your information. 

CrunkAtlanta may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that their users may 

frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most 

popular to customers or the general public.

CrunkAtlanta may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if 

required to do so pursuant to applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is 

deemed necessary or required to:

 _a) Conform to decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which_

 _may be served upon CrunkAtlanta and/or its website;_

 _b) Safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of CrunkAtlanta; and_

 _c) Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of_

 _users of crunkatlanta.com and/or the general public._

 **Children Under Age of 13**

CrunkAtlanta does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children 

under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such 

information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we 

shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from 

our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent 

or guardian permission to use this website.

 **  
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out**

All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving 

communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by 

way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an 

email that you wish to the email on our website. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from 

any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or 

opt-out. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites, such as this one where this 

document has been generated. CrunkAtlanta does not claim nor accept responsibility for 

any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we 

encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the 

privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable 

information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the 

information collected by our website. 

**Security**

CrunkAtlanta shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, 

procedural and technical security with respect to its offices and information storage facilities 

so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the 

user’s personal information under our control. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement**

CrunkAtlanta reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and 

as such we will post those change to our website homepage at crunkatlanta.com, so that 

our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will 

be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any 

point in time CrunkAtlanta decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on 

file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was 

initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time 

shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this 

separate manner. 

**  
Acceptance of Terms**

Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions 

stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement 

with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In 

addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes 

to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such 

changes. 

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our 

website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing 

address.

Email: crunkatlanta@gmail.com

"This policy is powered by [FormSwift](http://formswift.com/promissory-note),"
